Welcome to our lesson on cover letter writing.
欢迎来到求职信写作的课程
Sometimes called a motivation letter or letter of intent, a cover letter,
求职信有时称为自荐信 或者意愿书
is a way to introduce yourself to an employer and
是一种向雇主介绍自己的方式
tell them in your own words why you're the best person for the job.
用自己的话告诉他们为什么你是这个工作的最佳人选
In the past, cover letters accompanied resumes when the applicant
过去 当求职申请邮寄或者传真时
physically mailed or faxed in their job application.
求职信往往会附带在简历中
Nowadays, for the most part, they still accompany resumes but
现在 大多数情况 它们还是会附带在简历中
in online submission.
只是变成了网上提交
A cover letter may manifest itself in different ways.
求职信可以以不同的方式表现
Sometimes a cover letter is required, sometimes they are expected but
有时 求职信是必须的 有时虽然被期望
optional.
但也是可选的
Sometimes they are optional and they may not look like a letter.
有时它们是可选的 并且可能看起来不像一封信
When I applied to Udacity, I submitted a cover letter.
当我申请 Udacity 的时候 我就提交了一封求职信
However, I have co-workers who didn't submit any additional information, or
但是 我也有同事并没有提交任何额外信息
wrote a short paragraph instead of full pledge letter.
或者只是写了一小段 而不是整封信
Sometimes, a cover letter isn't expected or requested at all, but
有时 求职信也可能完全不需要
you still need to write a sure introduction.
但你还是需要写一个确切的自我介绍
In the past three years, I've applied to jobs with all four
过去三年 我申请工作时
of these types of cover letter requirements.
遇到过所有以上四种求职信的要求
And I opted to submit a letter to all of them.
并且我对所有申请都选择了提交求职信
I didn't write any of them from scratch, but
当然任何一封我都不是从头开始写的 而是
edited a copy of a letter I had been working on throughout my professional
编辑了一封求职信的副本 上面写着
experience, beginning from when I applied to my first ever job.
从我申请第一份工作开始 所有的工作经历
Although I didn't get an offer from every job I applied to,
虽然我没有得到每一份工作的录用通知 (offer)
I did get an in-person interview for over 75% of them.
但其中超过75%的都给了我面试的机会
Cover letters really help.
求职信真的很有帮助
After this lesson,
在这节课之后
you'll be prepared to tackle any of these application requirements.
你将准备好如何应对所有的这些申请要求
Before we move forward, if you haven't completed the course on conducting
在我们继续之前 如果你还没有完成
a successful job search or if you need a refresher, go back and review
寻找工作机会这门课程 或者需要复习的话 回去复习
the three things you need in order to conduct an effective job search.
进行有效的求职所需要的三件事情
Know what you want, research to understand what the employer wants, and
知道你想要什么 调查了解雇主想要什么 还有
be open to opportunity.
对机会开放
Once you've got that down, let's begin.
当你完成这些之后 就让我们开始这一课吧